importatlanta.com 2005-12-22

# IMPORTATLANTA.COM >>> your only source for import coverage & scene...

  |   | 

Privacy Policy (terms & services): 

IMPORTATLANTA.COM (a.k.a IA) respects your privacy. That's why we have created this Privacy Statement to explain how and why we collect certain information online, and how we use that information. This statement also explains how you can prevent collection of certain information about yourself, if you choose. Please take a few moments to read our Privacy Statement. This statement applies to all information we collect from visitors to the Importatlanta.com Web site / Message Board. 

As Importatlanta.com is constantly innovating and enhancing our site and message forums it provides to its users, this Privacy Statement will also continue to change to match our changes. As such, we reserve the right to change this statement to match the changes we make at anytime. If we make any changes to this statement, we will add a statement of the date below to reflect such changes. When you visit our site we encourage you to check the Privacy Statement to ensure you are aware of all statements. When viewing Importatlanta.com you agree to all terms and statements posted in the Privacy Statement. At anytime you do not agree with something in our Privacy Statement it is up to you to leave the site. 

However, regardless of how this Privacy Statement may change or evolve over time, Importatlanta.com will not collect or maintain your private and personally identifiable information without your consent. Further, if you consent to give us your personal information, we will keep it confidential and will not sell, license or disclose your personal information to any third party without your consent, unless we are compelled to do so under the law or to comply with a court order. 

**_Types of Information We Collect:_**  
Generally, you are free to browse Importatlanta.com site without submitting any personal information. We do not collect any of your personal information (such as a name, address or e-mail address) when you visit the Importatlanta.com, Unless... You register to use our site or otherwise agree to submit to us such information. As part of such processes, you have the opportunity to decline further promotional materials or other notifications from us regarding special information from Importatlanta.com.. 

**_Registration on Our Site:_**  
Importatlanta.com requires users who want to participate in our message board to register. In order to register, you must provide us with a username (which does not have to be your real name), password and a valid e-mail address. This allows us to protect our community from abusive postings and provides a verifiable point of contact should legal questions arise. At any time, you have the ability to keep your e-mail address hidden from other users by selecting that option within your user profile.When you register, you have the option of providing some additional information such as occupation, interests, and homepage URL. This optional information is made available to other bulletin or message board users to foster a sense of community. If you have any concerns about providing this information, simply leave the fields blank and your registration will still be processed. IF YOU ARE UNDER 18 YEARS OF AGE you are not allowed to participate in the Importatlanta.com Forums, or to provide any personal information on our site. Upon registering at Importatlanta.com you agree to all terms of our privacy statement. If at anytime you decided to leave IA you still are bound to this privacy statement. We at IA do not delete user accounts, but we can at anytime lock or ban your account at your request. If we find that you have broken any of the rules of the forum listed below, we at IA reserve the right to lock or ban your account/IP address until we see fit. If you have any questions about registering on our site please email:[ webmaster@importatlanta.com](mailto:%20%20webmaster@importatlanta.com)

_**Rules on Message Boards:**_  
It is important for you to remain aware that when you provide personal information (e.g., last name, address, phone number) in a posting on any message board, that information is available to any other person or user having access and use of that message board, and may be used by someone in a manner unintended by you. For that reason, we discourage you from offering any personally identifying information within a posting to any message board. IA uses Mods or moderators to watch our forums for post that we do not want on our site. These Mods or moderators are not paid nor do they work for IA, but they do have a say in how the forum runs. Any post that any IA Staff member or Mod finds that needs to be deleted, edited, or locked will be. No reason is needed to do so. Types of post that fall into this would be: bashing IA Staff / Mods / Members / - Sponsors, extreme language/hostility, threats, pics of illegal nature, post of illegal activities/products, and anything else that may confilct with any laws, etc...

_***** Importatlanta.com Staff or Mods are not responsible for what is posted or done by any Staff Member/Mod/User/Sponsor that might affect you emotionally, mentally, or physically. This is a FREE PUBLIC forum, eveything that can be thought of or done in public and more is normally acceptable on our site under the Rules of the Message Board. Everyone has opinions, sometimes they are not the same as you or I, but everyone is entitled to them; unless they confilct with our rules. If at anytime you feel offended by something on IA it is up to you to contact an IA staff member or leave the site. *****_

**_Contact for Privacy Inquiries:_**  
If you have any questions about this Privacy Statement or other questions about privacy on Importatlanta.com, please contact:[Info@importatlanta.com](mailto:%20%20Info@importatlanta.com)

Importatlanta.com is Privately owned and operated.   
Site Maitained By [5pointStudios.com  
](http://www.5pointstudios.com%20/)Site Hosted By [WireSix.com](http://www.wiresix.com/)  
Message Board Provided By vBULLETIN and  
maintained by Importatlanta.com's Moderators and Administrators.  
2001- 2004  
Reagards,  
Julio Morillo  
Founder/Owner

(Updated Feb. 16th, 2005,,, changed some wording and added some statement. This update will be posted on the message board.)  
(Updated April 2003,,, added wording and changes made to suit the new IA. Was posted boldly on homepage for all to agree to.)

|    
---|---|---|---
